hello youtube and welcome back to my
channel this is buddy golfer
and today we have another unboxing of
a golf product and guys i am so excited
about this one so it is something that
i've been looking into for the last or a
few weeks
because my range finder that i was using
over in oman stopped working just before
i left
and i knew that there was a new
rangefinder coming
out onto the market so i've now managed
to get my hands
on one so without further ado
in here is the new rangefinder
um so guys this is the new rangefinder
here
uh it comes in a very fancy box
it is from a company called bushnell
and as it says here is the t
this sorry the tour v5 shift
okay so this is new for 2020
i know that we're actually near the end
of 2020
but when i was over in oman these were
very very expensive so hence i didn't
get one
okay um there is two different
types of this two or v5
so there is the shift which is this one
here
and there is just the normal standard
2 v5 and i will go into the differences
between the two of these throughout this
video
okay um so this is the box that it came
in
which is very fancy and it does have
some of the details
on the back here and without further to
do
so excited um we have
if i can get out of the box this
so guys this as you can see is very
small
okay um it is only four and a half
inches
in length it is one and a half
inches in width it is three inches
in height and weighs eight
ounces okay um so i do have
quite small hands and if you actually
look at the size of this
it is absolutely perfect in my hand
okay um unfortunately none of these
are waterproof which
when playing over obviously in scotland
or if you are maybe playing over in
thailand like what i did
um last year then you do get
the occasional rain showers
so that may be something that might be
very good
in the future um
but so far looking at this
it is absolutely fantastic okay
um so going by the bushnell
website it speaks about size speed and
accuracy have been evolved
in this new generation of tech the
previous one
was the v4 um this one
does have pin seeker technology which
does have a jolt system which
means it does vibrate very slightly
in your hand same as what the v4 did
okay uh but this one has
when you look through here um
it actually gives you a red ring around
the circumference of
the eyepiece yeah just to
give you another um indication that you
are actually locked on
to the target so the target may be
the pin so you may be on like a par 3
hole as an example and you may be trying
to get the yardage
for that um if you're potentially on a
par 4 or a par
5 what you may be trying to identify
is the distance for any hazards
so you could also do that on a pathway
as well so that may be a tree line
it may be bunkers it may be water
etc um and this does give you
all of that information okay
so this particular model does have
this silver button here and it is
actually a
slide mechanism so red
is if it doesn't have the slope
which i will speak about in a second or
if you use the slope so when you are
actually looking
through the eyepiece here and you are
locked
onto a pin as an example it will
show you in either yards or meters
and you can change that by pressing this
button
here so depending in which country that
you are potentially playing
or where you come from um which is very
good
so this never used to be on
the actual body of
the v4 you actually had to go into the
settings to change this
whereas now you can actually do it um
literally by pressing a button okay um
the other thing that you do have is this
eyepiece here
does uh turn very similar to
a set binoculars and it has up to
six times magnification and
the eyepiece compared with the v4
which i believe was up to about 35 to 40
percent
for the visibility uh and
clarity this is now up to 70
so it's very very clear when you are
actually looking through
the eyepiece which
after reading the reviews and watching
several videos
on this it actually mentions that one of
the
advantages of this is when
the weather conditions are starting to
get
duller so whether or not it is
potentially going to be raining
or if you are actually playing early
morning or
later on in the day or if you're
actually playing in
fog okay um so it has actually
improved massively over
the v4 but also against other
manufacturers
as well okay so
you know it is very very lightweight
it's great
colors are fantastic and
on this side you do have a thing
called a bite technology
uh so this is uh actually a magnet
so if you are using a golf
trolley or a golf buggy
and it is the correct type of metal
then this will actually stick to the
side
and it has up to seven pounds of
pool required so even if you are
actually going over quite rough
terrain then it should not fall off
okay so as an example if this was
the pillar on the front of one of the
gulf buggies like i used to use an oman
this would just attach straight onto the
side of it
and then when you're ready you then
obviously just disconnect
this so this is something i did not have
on my previous rangefinder
and it then meant that you either needed
to
keep it inside one of the cup holders
or inside one of the small compartments
you do have within the golf buggy
so it does take up a wee bit of room so
this
is a great idea okay um i've not been
able to obviously try out yet
but yeah so far first impressions
are absolutely fantastic it is
subtle it is elegant
um and very very
easy to use also
it does come inside this very fancy
box and it does
have
this okay um
unsure slightly why the colors are
slightly different it's not
huge but this is more of a red whereas
this is an
orange so this obviously ties in more
with the color of
the box whereas i would have preferred
everything to be the same color but
that's maybe just me
this can hook onto
your bag very easily uh it could
potentially go
on to your belt if you wanted to slide a
belt through there but there's not
really much
give in that clasped open
is very easy
and it does have a small b here
and then you do have the zip facility
and it doesn't open fully because
of the two tabs here
but this then fits inside
and the good thing is you don't always
have to zip it up
if you don't want to you can just use
this yeah um so it's very very easy
to get in and out even the
small bag is very robust
uh it will obviously wipe down very
well because of the the material that
it's made from
um it does seem to be
really quite waterproof ish
potentially if you were to put a bit of
spray on it then it might be
slightly more waterproof but
very good so obviously having
the carabiner type clip here uh will
easily go
on to golf bag it's not very
big uh it's definitely not very heavy
either
so if you are obviously traveling and
you do not want that on the outside of
your bag you can easily slip it inside
your golf bag uh into one of the the
many pockets that you do have
and it will not take up much room
at all so um absolutely fantastic
i can now understand why
the bushnell
tour v5 shift gets
4.6 out of 5 stars
from the 294
reviews that it has had on the bushnell
website one good thing
also with this is there is an app
available so you can actually
track all of your shots going around the
golf course
as well so that's something that's
completely different
from every other range finder so i've
never ever had that
on any of the rangefinders i've ever
used
in the past so it is a feature that i
i'm really looking forward to getting to
use
so it can actually help track my shots
so
i can then get more of an idea regarding
the yardages
i hit every one of my clubs so i do
have other things i do use
or have used in the past that does
actually help
to track your shots because if anybody
has ever played
the game of golf then you know that you
need to know
your yardages so i'm finding here over
in scotland
that the yardages i hit my golf clubs
are completely different to the yardages
i would hit
the same club over in oman or thailand
dubai abu dhabi wherever i have played
previously
and at the moment it can be anything
from 15 to 20 yards
of a difference and i'm shorter
so obviously the air over here at the
moment is very cold
uh so it's very dense air uh
also the course
itself is very wet it's very muddy um
so the ball is not carrying as far and
it's definitely not
running as far as what it has done
in the past so you know
some of the games i've played recently
even using a driver and if you're
hitting 220 yards with a driver
your ball is actually ending up almost
within the divot that it's just left
within the pitch mark
so it's just not rolling out at all so
things like this
is fantastic it will hopefully take my
game to the next level which is one of
their scenes that they do have
and regarding your tour pros
99.3 percent of tour pros
use a bushnell rangefinder
so that's phenomenal that is virtually
every single player is
got their hands on one of the bushnells
so whether or not it may be a v4 or it
may be
this uh exact model to me
that shows how good that the
bushnell product is also you get a
two-year
limited warranty with the item
as well and going by the reviews the
customer service
that you do get from the company is
absolutely fantastic
as well so i am loving this
i cannot wait to get out onto the golf
course
and then to let everybody know
how it is so guys do please stick around
and i will tell you how it has gone
[Music]
okay guys so uh review
on the bushnell v5
tour shift as it is fantastic
so i have just played nine holes
up at edsel uh golf course which is
where i'm currently getting golf lessons
and it was absolutely fantastic i cannot
fault it at all so as i said earlier on
yes having it being waterproof may be
more of an advantage um so that's maybe
something that bushnell could
potentially look into
in the future but the ease that you
use this is just phenomenal so
um using the button here on
the top that then um
locks into the target that you are
aiming at
and i was actually standing on t
boxes on some of the holes and
literally zapping a flag that was 450
yards
almost 500 yards away from me and it was
doing it
straight away um these
greens and flags are actually surrounded
with trees
and it was not picking up the trees at
all
if i was actually aiming it for the flag
so
there is one thing that i would have
hoped
that i might have got which was uh
if you aim at one one item
so i.e the flag and then you potentially
aim
at the bunker to the side of the flag
it doesn't tell you the difference
between the two
um i'm not sure if that could ever be
done on any of the
the rangefinders but um
what i ended up having to do was zap the
flag
and then zap the bunker and then
actually have to try and calculate
out whatever the the distance was so it
may have been like 15 to 20 yards
as an example which wasn't
too hard to do but it would have been a
nice feature to have had
um but the screen looking through the
eye finder is great uh
very very clear the
writing is also very clear the jolt you
do feel it
the red ring didn't always appear if i'm
being perfectly honest with you
but it did appear a lot um and then
it does tell you the slope so what that
means
is that if the item that you are
detecting so ie the pin as an example
if it is above or below you
so it then calculates that and then it
tells you
how far away that you should actually
hit your shot
so as an example if you have a flag
that's 120 yards away
and the slope gives you a plus
two then it would actually tell you that
you need to
hit the ball 122 yards
to then get the ball into the hole yeah
so it's very very easy it's very easy to
understand
it tells you the information straight
away
and if you do press this button here
then it does change it from yards to
meters
and you could literally do that within
the the one shot yeah you do not have to
go into the settings
also if you switch this so it's not
showing the
the red then it does mean that you can
use this rangefinder in competitions
if you are a professional okay so this
is the main difference between
the two or v5 and the two v5
shift the tour v5 does not have the
slope
uh algorithm so it
it can be used in competitions yeah
this one if i'm just playing with
my my friends or if i'm just playing on
my own
then i can use that with the red
half circle uh displayed and then it
will give me the
the algorithm for the slope okay
so very very easy to switch between the
two
but you would obviously never do that if
you are in a competition
um very sturdy very easy to
hold on to so this thumb
um holder here um is
quite rough so it does make it very easy
to hold it does have a very small
battery
uh compartment here which is nice and
easy to get into
i could not use the bite technology
um i'm not sure the material that my
gulf buggy sorry gulf trolley is made
from
uh so it might only work with golf
buggies
but um this top area here it's all
raised and beveled as well which is
where your
two or three fingers would be at the
front and then
very easy to press um
so overall very very impressed
as i said though this front is a
slightly different color
to the the bag but
apart from that fantastic love it
five out of five bushnell this this is
fantastic
so i need to try and find out how to get
on to the
app because i couldn't find that out
this morning
um after i did the unboxing and
i still haven't managed to find the app
as yet
but it is mentioned on their website
so yeah great um
product and this rangefinder is under
400 pounds
so this is the the reason i was speaking
to you about earlier on that i
had not bought it when i was over an old
man
because when i was looking at the prices
in oman and also in dubai
they literally had not changed the
currency they'd not converted it
at all so it was almost double the price
so
i knew that i was coming back to the uk
very soon
so that was why i bought it over here
but absolutely fantastic
so the company that i bought this from
uh did give me a free gift which was
actually a new battery
uh which costs about eight pounds and it
is just a very very small battery
the delivery was next day
so that was great and i did get notified
as well
when the person was going to be coming
to deliver it
um so service fantastic
as well so i cannot recommend
this product any more than what i
already have done
as i said i would definitely give it
five out of five
so i'm very looking forward to using
this
for the next couple of years and also
trying to use the new
app as well for it um to try and
hopefully improve
my golf game so guys thank you very much
for uh viewing for liking
for subscribing it is very much
appreciated
please do not skip over the adverts
on the channel i do know that it can be
quite annoying sometimes watching
some of the adverts but without the
adverbs
then i will not get any revenue which
then means i cannot do
new things like this as well so it is
to try and help grow the channel which
is why
youtube does have the adverts on it so
please do not skip over
the adverts so please do like please do
comment please do share with your
friends and family
as well and look forward to
hearing from you all very soon
[Applause]
[Music]
great
bye
[Music]
you